very very deep charge unit which will
run all day you can turn it off and
leave it for hours I mean hours and you
can come back no power on the turn
ignition on hit the key instantly that
the vacuum goes onto that unit it is a
charge unit it runs it
starts you leave it
overnight and somewhere between
somewhere and about 3:00 in the morning
the unit seems to go
deep by
itself you can run it up to 12:00 at
night and the um the vehicle will still
start go out at 12:00 don't run it all
afternoon go out at 12:00 at night hit
the key causes a vacuum on the straight
onto the unit no power connected to it
it'll start I don't know what it'll
start but you leave till the morning
there must be a I don't know something
in the air or the cooling or the the
actual magnetism in the Earth or
something like that flattens it you
understand we have done some experiments
by hooking up a
1 I don't know little torch 1.5
1.5 um battery DC battery the strange
thing about it is if you have a large
battery and you have it to your unit all
the time it uses a heap of current
produces gas and you don't need all that
gas it produces as you see on on your
film and everything El said the gas or
the balls you don't that gas is not me
you have gas which will run it when you
disconnect all you don't need extra gas
so if you have a big battery it will use
it and if you leave a big battery
connected to the unit and turn your
motor off with a current going in it
will only take 10 minutes or more and
your battery out here will be dead but
you hook up a little 1.5 Vol battery and
you can leave it on there for as long as
you like and it does not affect the the
it doesn't flatten it it doesn't use in
it holds the potential over the unit
that that 1.5 volt battery does not
produce any gas while it is connected to
the unit
not but it holds potential on it we've
been driving in the river driving along
holding at say 60 M hour on the
accelerator and the motor at the car and
everything on the unit no G uh no power
connected to the unit and we have
connected this 1.5 Vol battery across
positive to negative and the car just
took off like you dropped the back of
gear without doing nothing and it does
not drain that 1.5 Vol battery you can
leave that battery on there day after
day after day and not run the vehicle in
it w flatten it put your big battery on
and flatten it in a few
minutes this stuff works very strangely
well you're saying that the 1.5 volt was
working really well and the as soon as
you put the 12v on it was going dropping
the 12v out differen is in current I
mean on 1.5 Vol you got no current only
12 you got plenty of current yeah but
while you got vacuum pulling on your M
while the car is going and you hook up
that 1.5 volt battery you get an
increase your car takes off like you
drop back again so
you the voled seems to be there than
current there's no current 1.5 Vol
anyway well it can't be volage either I
don't know what it is it is something in
your manifold the
uh the riv was pulling about
22 to
24 vacuum you know Ines um
vacuum and you can drop right down I've
had the the uh R down to about 2 lb
manifold vacuum and the car was idling
smooth as G you put on petrol and you
dropped down under say 12 the mother
don't go anymore she just St she stopped
She Stopped but I've had him running on
2B manifold vacuum not with acceleration
open with a motor just St right down to
that and the car is still going smooth
as glass that's physically by mechanics
I this impossible but it
happens while you're idling the polyan
unit was level when you increased the
acceleration normally logically the unit
by a heavier vacuum pulling on it should
have suck the unit in this didn't occur
the unit
expanded tremend it's expanded
tremendous that's on t two um and by
doing that what was happening was the
unit was
producing more gas than what was needed
and it seemed to be pulling off under
atmospheric pressure a unit puts out a
certain amount of pressure which you can
regulate and you know you can check
now if you have um vacuum you pull off a
certain amount of gas but between vacuum
and and atmospheric pressure there's a
difference the in the unit it seems that
the motor wants to pull off under vacuum
but it doesn't seem to use any of that
other gas what comes off
under uh atmospheric
pressure so when you cause a vacuum on
there you think you you can't uh even
out by pulling
um atmospher plus
vacuum why the polye units ex SP is
because the what it'll what will get off
Under Pressure atmosph pressure doesn't
use any of it for some reason and that
expands a unit and that's why it's so do
this because there is so much pressure
you can get off those units and it's
more than just what you can regulate off
atmospheric pressure because when you
put a vacuum on
you remove the 57 lb um pressure
atmospheric pressure and there is a
great big assistance of that gas but
kind move after that without vacuum so
we got our G to sit here now at nor but
we have our GES here for our pressure
here now is said it nor but we have the
57 lb in these things whatever the
pressure is on us now is removed on the
vacuum the vacuum can pull off what it
needs the unit can produce gas of own
accord without any current input if you
put in a current input and you put which
causes a heap of gas and you put vacuum
which you've seen on the on the um on
the tape it produces its own gas on the
vacuum when the unit is charged it's
only using what it vacuums there is a
mile of gas you can see on T there and
in the unit being produced under your
battery under charge or under your
normal
pressure when that pressure is removed
there is a super release and that
expands the unit out
tremendously you become very as it's on
tape before you become very inefficient
when you back off from the accelerator
that expansion of the poine unit then
transfers into your motor if you want to
slow
down what happens is you can't because
you're back off an the accelerator that
stops the vacuum on the unit that stops
that pressure
sucking your car doesn't slow down like
it normally does on petrol that pressure
expansion transfers into the manifold
and your car just keeps going and you go
for the brakes there noow manifold
vacuum brakes they're
gone with a solid unit you don't get any
extra expansion of gas at all and when
you back off an accelerator your car
does a nose dive should you slows down
like you RI the brakes on without
touching the brakes when you power on it
is there You' got what you want you can
have it with the current or without the
current it makes no
difference it's very strange solid unit
is a way to go but if you've got any
flexible hose or any flexible unit
whether it is thin
stainless any flexible hose you do have
about how much well on the on the um the
tube from the from the manifold I I was
running a tube I don't care what type of
tube you use it can be any metal it can
be copper it can be um stainless can be
grass I don't care it doesn't matter
because there's no pollution from your
motor backwards because your motor is
negative but your unit is positive and
if you join the a metal hose from your
manifold or car to the it's got to be
that way you can't have a negative
exterior to the unit so you can have
this see what what what other people
have with my ideas me explain them to
what they've done on their own is run
metal thinking that it's the wrong way
to go hook metal tubes up from the unit
which were positive all the way down
Milly to the motor and then put in a a
tuun it didn't work because apparently
your the gas and everything else what is
coming off it's splitting from negative
towards positive they say it is a
positively charged
what do you
call whatever whatever is coming off is
supposedly so so other people have seen
without men not it is positively charged
now it if it is that way and it's trying
to then get to a negative it's been
split from a negative out it does not go
to a positive because off your positive
walls gas comes off in or if you're
negative gas goes out it is not a
magnetic attraction toward from negative
towards positive you can see on film
there it comes off and goes up goes away
if you bring them in Too Close they
fight each other they cause a barrier
where they just both of them just can't
get off so it's not this one pulling
that one to there or this one pulling
that one to there they are separated
they want to get off if they are a
positively charged uh particle they are
looking for a negative to flow down if
you run a positive tube all the way from
your unit down down towards your motor
and put in a small bit right up there is
neutral there's no water there's no
current there's nothing on that the
current stays in the water between your
negative and your positive it stays in
the water because negative is not
connected to the
positive so that thing there is a
positive and apparently what happens is
the gas thingss to attract straight to
the wall it's good but if you have a
negative from your motor back to very to
the unit that is a negative and if it is
a positive I don't know any of these
things it's all experimental if that is
this is the way I've had it working if
it's a negative tube the positively
charged things seem to see it up that
line they jump towards it they don't
blend into it they just get a grease
lightning slip straight through down
into the motor without any
restriction on that copper tube I was
showing
you which was polluted badly one side of
the copper tube was connected to the
unit where the water was and everything
else and that turned out polluted dark
green crystallized
G that far further up the tube was clear
and clean because it was not there near
where the positive charge stuff is so
your copper if you say a pollutes it
only pollutes on the positive side but
it has to be a solid piece right solid
if it can expand in or contract when you
put the vacuum onto the
motor it will suck in because it's not
producing any gas but if your unit like
a polye or anything else I've showed you
that if if you have a um a unit which
the plates in it aren't strong enough to
put off the gas you need you should have
that little bottle put on this now to
sort of show the bottle because it only
had very thin wise would run the car
would stay expanded or stay to its size
while you're idling when you
accelerate the very soft wall plastic
cordal bottle went in because those
plates could not put off the gas to
compensate but when your plates are big
enough and strong enough to put off all
the gas you want then it doesn't suck in
it expands and becomes very dangerous
the sucking in would be great your motor
wouldn't run because you run out of gas
it's not sufficient but when you got too
much and you'll never ever
hit with that you'll never hit the right
plates under Expendable unit to
compensate for each running of the motor
you would hit you you hook it up and be
idle or halfway or full rep or whatever
you would never be able to strike it and
keep anything to be able to accelerate
and de accelerate that's where the
stainless one does everything solid
stainless does everything you have soft
stainless forget it too we've already
had that you've seen the unit build take
very thin stainless experience and
that's worse more dangerous because it
is Solider and if it lets go it's gone
you just rip you AP you seen balloons go
off we've got them in a very flexible
rubber um container the gas is sealed in
there but when it gets out it just
doesn't there's a great big ring you
have your hands close take your hair off
your hands it's not gas it's not a flam
it's the in rushing it causes it
straight in you get your Gloom back it
tears it so if this gas goes off and
it's pressurized there it's trying to
get out but soon as it can get out and
it meets a bit of air bang the polye
units off seen expand out you can't I
don't know how much pressure you reckon
you can push by a thumb on one of those
Lids of that poly stuff but I reckon you
could push 4050 lb even if you stood on
it you wouldn't bend it out now hooked
up to to vacuum of the motor those Lids
I've had them expanding out an inch to
an inch and a half there's no way in the
world you can get that amount of
pressure you take that unit seal it off
down to the to a um gas station and you
put the air hose on there and you can
build up 100 lb pressure and I bet you
that lid won't Bend out the way it was
under there imagine that gas getting out
if it just split and got out it would
take everything G man no worries
so don't use
it